Little Magazine Collection, 1895-1976 (bulk 1965-1976)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 2, #1, Winter (#5), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 2, #2, Spring (#6), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 2, #3, Summer (#7), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 3, #1-2, Winter/Spring (#9), 1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 3, #3, Summer (#10), 1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 3, #4, Fall (#11), 1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Journal for the Protection of All Beings, San Francisco, #1, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Journal of the New American Literature and the Arts, Stanford, California, #2, Fall, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Journal 31, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, Summer, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Juego de Hojas, Mexico, #1, September, 1966-October, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Kauri, New York City, #19, March, 1967-April, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Klactoveedsedsteen, Heidelberg, Germany, #4, Fall/Winter, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Kulchur, New York City, v. 3, Autumn (#11), 1963 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Kumquat, #2, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Kumquat, Endsburg Falls, Vermont, #3, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- L.A.201, Idaho State College, Pocatello, Idaho, #2, May, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- The Lace Review, Newark, New Jersey, v. 1, #3, November, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- The Lake Superior Review, Ironwood, Michigan, v. 4, #3, Winter, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- The Lampeter Muse, Bard College, Annandale-on-Hudson, New York, Spring, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #5 (Book 1), May, 1895-April, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #6 (Book 1), May, 1895-April, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #7 (Book 1), May, 1895-April, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #8 (Book 1), May, 1895-April, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #9 (Book 1), May, 1895-April, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #10 (Book 1), May, 1895-April, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #11 (Book 1), May, 1895-April, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #12 (Book 1), May, 1895-April, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #13 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #14 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #15 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #16 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #17 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #18 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #19 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #20 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- The Lark, San Francisco #21 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #22 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #23 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #24 (Book 2), May, 1896-April, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- The Lark, San Francisco, #25 (The Epi-Lark), May, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- The Last Cookie, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Latitudes, Houston, v. 2, #2, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Laugh Literary and Man the Humping Guns, Los Angeles, #1, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Laugh Literary and Man the Humping Guns, Los Angeles, v. 1, #2, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- The Left, Davenport, Iowa, v. 1, #1, September, 1931 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- The Leprechaun Review, New York City, v. 1, #2, Summer, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Letras de Ayer y de Hoy, Mexico, v. 3, (#31), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Letras de Ayer y de Hoy, Mexico (#37), January, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Letras de Ayer y de Hoy, Mexico (#38), March, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Letras de Ayer y de Hoy, Mexico (#39), April, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Letras de Ayer y de Hoy, Mexico (#40), May, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Letras de Ayer y de Hoy, Mexico (#41), August, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Letras de Cotopaxi, Ecuador (#17), February, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Lillabulero, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, v. 2, #1, Winter (#5), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Lillabulero, Northwood Narrows, New Hampshire (#14), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Lines, New York City, #3, February, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Lines, New York City, #4, March, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Lines, New York City, #6, November, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Lip, Philadelphia, #1, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- The Lit, Notre Dame, Indiana, v. 1, #4, January 13, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- The Literary Supplement, Oslo, Norway (#3), November 10, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- The Literary Supplement, Oslo, Norway (#4), March, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- The Literary Supplement, Oslo, Norway (#5), March, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- The Literary Supplement, Oslo, Norway (#6), March, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- The Literary Supplement, Oslo, Norway (#13), December, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- The Literary Supplement, Oslo, Norway (#14), December, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- The Literary Supplement, Oslo, Norway (#15), December, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- The Literary Supplement, Oslo, Norway (#21), December, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Literature & Ideology, Toronto, Canada (#11), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Litmus, Seattle, #1, circa 1967 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Litmus, Seattle, #2, circa 1967 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Litmus, Seattle, #3, circa 1967 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Litmus, Seattle, #4, circa 1967 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Litmus, Seattle, #5-6, circa 1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Litmus, Oakland, California, #8, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Litmus, Berkeley, California, #9, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Litmus, Salt Lake City, #10, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Litmus, Salt Lake City, #12, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
- The Little Man, Cincinnati, Ohio, pt. 3, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- The Little Review, Huntington, West Virginia, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- The Little Review, Huntington, West Virginia, v. 1, #2, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
- The Little Review, Huntington, West Virginia, v. 3, #2 (#6), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- The Little Review, Huntington, West Virginia, v. 4, #1 (#7), 1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- The Little Square Review, Santa Barbara, California, #3, Summer (The Purgatory Poems, Edwin Fussell), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- The Little Square Review, Santa Barbara, California, #4, Fall (Twenty Poems, Barry Spacks), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- The Little Square Review, Santa Barbara, California, #5-6, Spring/Summer, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- The Little Square Review, Santa Barbara, California, #7, Summer, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- The Little Square Review, Santa Barbara, California, #8, Summer, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- The Little Square Review, Santa Barbara, California, #9-10, Spring/Summer, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- llama's Almanac, Gloucester, Massachusetts, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- local earth, Portland, Oregon, #2, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Logos Review, San Francisco, #3, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Look Quick, Boulder, Colorado, #4, Spring, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Loon, Santa Rosa, California, #1, October, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Lost and Found Times, Columbus, Ohio, #3, May, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Ludd's Mill, Huddersfield, England, #5, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Ludd's Mill, Huddersfield, England, #7, undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Ludd's Mill, Huddersfield, England, #10, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
- M, San Francisco, #1, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Madrona, Seattle, v. 1, #4, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Madrona, Seattle, v. 2, #5, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Madrona, Seattle, v. 2, #6, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Madrona, Seattle, v. 2, #7, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- The Magdalene Syndrome Gazette, San Francisco, #1, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
- The Magdalene Syndrome Gazette, San Francisco, #2, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
- The Magdalene Syndrome Gazette, San Francisco, #3, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- The Magdalene Syndrome Gazette, San Francisco, #4, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
- The Magdalene Syndrome Gazette, San Francisco, #5, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
- The Magdalene Syndrome Gazette, San Francisco, #6-7, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Magazine, New York City, #1, circa 1965 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Magazine, New York City, #3, circa 1965 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Magazine, New York City, #4, circa 1965 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Magazine, New York City (editor, Kirby Congdon), #4 ("Mag 4"), 1969 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- The Magazine of Further Studies, #5, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
- The Magazine of Further Studies, #6, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Maguey, El Cerrito, California, #1, May, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Maguey, El Cerrito, California, #2, Autumn, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Maguey, El Cerrito, California, #3-4, Winter, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Maguey, El Cerrito, California, #5, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- The Mainstreeter, Stevens Point, Wisconsin, #7, Summer/Fall (Poets of the Red River, #4), 1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Maitreya, Berkeley, California, #1, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Maitreya, Berkeley, California, #2, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- The Malahat Review, University of Victoria, Victoria, Canada, #35, July, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Mandala, Madison, Wisconsin, #2, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Mandala, Madison, Wisconsin, #3, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Mandala, Madison, Wisconsin, #4, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Mandala, Madison, Wisconsin, #6, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Mandrake, London, v. 2, #9, Summer/Autumn, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Manhattan Review, New York City, #1, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Manhattan Review, New York City, v. 1, #2, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Manhattan Review, New York City, v. 1, #3, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Man-Root, San Francisco, #1, August, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Man-Root, San Francisco, #2, January, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Man-Root, San Francisco, #3, August, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Man-Root, San Francisco, #4, February, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Maps, New York City, #2, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Maps, Shippensburg, Pennsylvania, #5, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Mariner, College of Marin, Kentfield, California, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Masks, Stanford, California, v. 1, #1, Fall, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Matador, New York City, #1, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Matador Home News, New York City, June, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Matrix, Los Angeles, v. 3, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Matter, Annandale-on-Hudson, New York, #4, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Measure, Pullman, Washington, #1, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Measure, Bowling Green, Ohio, #3, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Measure, Bowling Green, Ohio, #5, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Meatball, San Francisco, #1, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Meatball, San Francisco, #3 (Battlefield Syrup, Douglas Blazek), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Mester, Mexico, #7, June, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Mester, Mexico, #8, July, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Mester, Mexico, #9, August, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Metamorphosis, Wayne, Pennsylvania, #3, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Michigan Hot Apples, Bloomfield Hills, Michigan, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Michigan Hot Apples, Bloomfield Hills, Michigan, #2, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Micromegas, University of Iowa, Iowa City, Iowa, v. 3, #1, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Micromegas, University of Iowa, Iowa City, Iowa, v. 3, #2, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
- The Middle R, Eastern Oregon College, La Grand, Oregon, #10, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- The Middle R, Eastern Oregon College, La Grand, Oregon, #11, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- The Middle R, Eastern Oregon College, La Grand, Oregon, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- The Mile High Underground, Denver, v. 1, #6, Fall, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Mimeo, Cambridge, Massachusetts, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Man, Los Angeles, v. 1 (2nd series), #1, Summer, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Mistletoe, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Modern Poetry in Translation, London, England, #2, Summer, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Modern Poetry in Translation, London, England, #3, Spring, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Modularist Review, Cambridge, Massachusetts, #1, Summer, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Modularist Review, Cambridge, Massachusetts, #2, Summer, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Mojo Mavigator (E), Glen Ellyn, Illinois, #1, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Mojo Mavigator (E), Ann Arbor, Michigan, #3, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Mojo Mavigator (E), Glen Ellyn, Illinois, #4, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Monocle, New York City, v. 3, #2, Spring, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Montana Gothic, Missoula, Montana, #2, Spring, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- The Montparnasse Review, The American Center for Students and Artists, Paris, #2, Summer, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Monument in Cantos and essays, Columbia, Missouri, v. 1, #1, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Monument in Cantos and essays, Columbia, Missouri, v. 1, #2, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Monument in Cantos and essays, Columbia, Missouri, v. 1, #3, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Monument in Cantos and essays, Columbia, Missouri, v. 2, #1, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Moondance, Memphis, Tennessee, v. 1, #1, Autumn, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Moondance, Memphis, Tennessee, v. 2, #1, Spring, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Moonlight Review, Brooklyn, New York, v. 1, #3, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Moonstones, Sacramento, California, #3, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Moonstones, Sacramento, California, #4 (and Runcible Spoon 3), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Mother, Galesburg, Illinois, #5, Summer, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Mother, Galesburg, Illinois, #7, Summer, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Mother, Galesburg, Illinois, #8, Summer, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- motive, Nashville, Tennessee, January, 1964-February, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- motive, Nashville, Tennessee, v. 27, #2, November, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- motive, Nashville, Tennessee, v. 29, #6-7, March, 1969-April, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Mt. Adams Review, Cincinnati, Ohio, v. 2, #4, Winter, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Mt. Adams Review, Cincinnati, Ohio, v. 2, #5, Fall, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Mt. Adams Review, Cincinnati, Ohio, v. 2, #6, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Mountain Review, v. 2, #1, December, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Mountain Summer, Sewanee, Tennessee, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #1, May, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #2, September, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #3, December, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #4, March, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, June, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #6, September, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #7, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #8, March, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #9, July, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Mouth of the Dragon, New York City, #10, December, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Mulch, New York City, v. 1, #1, April, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Mulch, New York City, v. 2, #1, Spring, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Museo del Oro, Colombia, #119, June, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Mutiny, Northport, New York, v. 4, #1, Fall/Winter, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- My Own Mag, Barnet, England, February, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Nadine, Croton, Connecticut, March, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- The Natoma Free Sun, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, April 25, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- The Natoma Free Sun, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, July 25, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Nebula, North Bay, Canada, #1, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Neon, Brooklyn, New York, #3, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Neon, Brooklyn, New York, #4, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Nevermind, Sacramento, California, v. 1, #1, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 1, #1, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 1, #2, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 2, #1, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 2, #2, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 2, #3, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 4, #1-2, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 4, #3, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 5, #1-2, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 5, #3, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- New Collage, Sarasota, Florida, v. 6, #1, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- New Durham, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
- New Editions, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, Fall, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- New Editions, Berkeley, California, #2, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
- The New Hampshire Poet, Rye Beach, New Hampshire, #1, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
- The New Lantern Club Review, Houston, Texas, #1, December, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- The New Lantern Club Review, Houston, Texas, #2, Summer, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- New Measure, Oxford, England, #1, Autumn, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- New Measure, Oxford, England, #1, Winter, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- New Measure, Oxford, England, #3, Summer, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- New Measure, Oxford, England, #4, Winter, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- New Measure, Northwood, England, #5, Spring, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- New Measure, Northwood, England, #7, Winter, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- New Measure, Northwood, England, #8, Winter, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- New Measure, Northwood, England, #9, Summer, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- New Measure, Northwood, England, #10, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- New Poetry, London, England, #30, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- New Student Review, State University of New York at Buffalo (reprints), 1967 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- New Voices, New York City, #1, Winter, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- New Voices, New York City, #2, Winter, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 1, #4, June 22, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 1, #6, July 8, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 1, #7, July 22, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 1, #8, August 9, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 1, #9-10, September 11, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 1, #12, November 11, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 1, #13-14, November 26, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 1, #15-16, December 12, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- The New York Culture Review, New York City, v. 2, #2-4 (#26), June 26, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- New York Poetry, New York City, v. 1, #1, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- New York Times, New York City, #1, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- New York Times, New York City, #2, March, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- New York Times, New York City, #3, Winter, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, July, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Nexus, San Francisco, September, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 1, #5, Spring, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 1, #6, Summer, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 1, #7, Fall, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 2, #1 (#8), January, 1965-February, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 2, #2 (#9), March, 1965-April, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 2, #3 (#10), May, 1965-June, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 2, #4 (#11), July, 1965-August, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 2, #5 (#12), September, 1965-October, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 2, #6 (#13), November, 1965-December, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Nexus, San Francisco, v. 3, #1 (#14), January, 1967-February, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Niagara Frontier Review, Buffalo, New York, Summer, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Niagara Frontier Review, Buffalo, New York, Spring (cover); Fall (title page), 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- The Niagara Magazine, Buffalo, New York, #2, Winter, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- The Niagara Magazine, Buffalo, New York, #3, Summer, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Nimrod, Tulsa, Oklahoma, v. 4, #3, Spring, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- The Ninth Circle, Las Cruces, New Mexico, November, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Nitty-Gritty, Pasco, Washington, v. 1, #2, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- No Walls Broadsheet, Cardiff, Wales, #13, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Nomad, Culver City, California, #10-11, Autumn, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Noonday, New York City, #1, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Noonday, New York City, #2, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Noose, New York City, #4, May 4, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Noose, New York City, #5, June 1, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Noose, New York City, #6, June 22, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Noose, New York City, #8, September 15, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Noose, New York City, #14, April 27, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Noose, New York City, #15, May 17, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Noose, New York City, #16, May 30, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Noose, New York City, #17, July 12, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Noose, New York City, #18, September 13, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- The Norman Hackforth, Cambridge, England, undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
- north country Anvil, Millville, Minnesota, #10, February, 1974-March, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- North Country Medicine, Canton, New York, #2, circa 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- North Country Medicine, Canton, New York, #3, March, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- North Country Medicine, Canton, New York, #4, March, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- North Country Medicine, Canton, New York, #5, March, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- North Country Medicine, Canton, New York, #6, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Northeast, Temple, Maine, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Northeast, LaCrosse, Wisconsin, Fall, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Northeast, LaCrosse, Wisconsin, Spring/Summer, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Northeast Rising Sun, Baltimore, v. 1, #2, May, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Northwood's Journal, Bigfork, Minnesota, v. 4, #4, May, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- A Nosegay in Black, Saint Louis, v. 1, #1, Autumn, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Nothing Doing in London, London, England, #2, January, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Now, London, England, v. 7, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Now Save the Dead, Tampa, Florida, #2, November, 1971-December, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- La Nueva Sangre, New York City, v. 1, #3, September, 1968-October, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- La Nueva Sangre, New York City, v. 1, #6, March, 1969-April, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Number 1, University of Kansas City, Missouri, May, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Oasis, Kingston Polytechnic, Kingston-upon-Thames, England, #4, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Oberlin Quarterly, Oberlin College, Oberlin, Ohio, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Oblique, University of Illinois, Champaign, Illinois, v. 2, #1, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Obscurologist Papers, Madison, Wisconsin, #2, Summer, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Obsidian, Palo Alto, California, #3, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Occident, University of California, Berkeley, California, Spring, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Occident, University of California, Berkeley, California, v. 1 (new series), Spring/Summer, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Occident, University of California, Berkeley, California, v. 3, Spring/Summer, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 25)